That's the Bottle City of Kandor.
(Penny:)Uh-huh.
(Leonard:)You see, Kandor was the capital city
of the planet Krypton.
It was miniaturized by Brainiac
before Krypton exploded...
(Leonard:)...and then rescued by Superman.
(Penny:)Oh, nice.
(Leonard:)It's a lot cooler
when girls aren't looking at it.
(Penny:)Here, why don't you put these on
while I find a shirt and sport coat?
- Great, be right back.
- Where are you going? Put them on.
- Here?
- Oh, are you shy?
- No, I'm not shy.
- Don't worry, I won't look.
I know you won't. Why would you look?
There's nothing to see. Not noth...
- Sweetie, put the pants on.
- I'm gonna put them on.
So, you know, isn't there some way
you and Sheldon could compromise...
...on this presentation thing?
(Leonard:)No, no. Scientists do not compromise.
Our minds are trained to synthesize facts
and come to inarguable conclusions.
(Sheldon:)Not to mention,
Sheldon is bat-crap crazy.
(Penny:)What is this?